Yes
master so I have a few lessons for you
today all right so lesson one when you
go to McDonald's and they ask you if
you'd like a side of fries with that you
say no Genji you [__] say no it'll be
a true test of your will I say no Genji
they are not Genji I am
Genji God damn it Genji listen to your
master all right rule two or wait not
rule two I like my side of fries you're
not allowed to have fries
Soldier yeah you're too old the sodium
does not do good for your body Soldier
all right lesson two never ask a girl
where she wants to go to eat because
then she'll say wherever you want to go
and we are going to get sushi no listen
L it's not done Genji all right so then
you'll pick a place to go and then
she'll disagree with you and then
that'll lead into a fight and then you
both wind up hungry and
mad so don't don't ever do that
I would keep that in mind and the last
thing is I like
turtles Angela will not like that she'll
not Mercy won't like that I like
turtles oh you died even my master I put
my healing nut sack on you so Master you
are supposed to teach me a lesson I just
taught you three lessons
Genji I do not find much value in your
lessons
monster all I want to know is where the
bathroom
is
what Reaper shouldn't you go reap
something okay I'm going to be honest I
don't uh I don't got I don't got an
answer for that one Reaper it is not
wise to deny the master an
answer he has many
balls and considers
himself extremely masculine
kill this robot
please nice one
Reaper stupid robot kill your brother
I'm ready to unleash my blade Master do
I have permission permission
granted [__]
monkey I have your back
Mercy what' I tell you about looking at
Mercy's butt Genji
Master can I have an exception just this
on no all right everyone step into my
penis I mean my
Iris master I need a
ball behind you ass nicely give me a
ball master all right Genji look at this
new Kung Fu form that I'm going to teach
you one day check this out
what that was very scary
Master hello Road
Hog I like your nipple ring I
know do you want to be my friend Road
Hub yes or
no he gave you the thumbs up okay you
are very Sharky
today your brother has killed many more
my brother Hanzo he is a disgrace to our
family he is nothing but a miserable
Soul why am I not
great because you are
bold
what you have no
hair I can still be great with no
hair I doubt that there are many great
people with no hair um let's see Krillin
from Dragon Ball Z
he dies so many you look like a metallic
version of Krillin master I
do and then there's Mr
Clean um he is a
slave
what he is always cleaning he is a
slave I want to kill somebody with my
blue
balls I heard that is a very dangerous
thing to have
so Genji what lessons have I taught you
today I want you to I don't
remember wow something about nuggets did
you say something about chicken nuggets
I believe
so finger
sniff what an interesting choice of a
name you always got to sniff your
fingers once in a
while that's especially when you're done
pooping yep that's lesson number four
Genji by the way
two finger sniffs a day makes the pain
go
away that is a good lesson
Master go chill with
Bastion Bas you both are machines right
hello he is a made in
[Laughter]
China no
how
[Laughter]
unfortunate Genji turned into a popsicle
what the [__]